<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Alpaca Consultants</title>
    <link>https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Alpaca Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:53:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whire</title>
      <link>https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/whire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/whire/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Whire is a Singaporean Tech Startup which helps companies hire great people faster through its platform and a top tier community of hiring ambassadors, saving companies hours on pre-screening and outreach efforts as well as thousands of dollars on job ads and agency fees without compromising candidate quality.
Motivation Benjamin Marsili (founder of Whire) hired me to help him build a recruiting network platform for companies to;
Broadcast jobs from LinkedIn (and other sources) Directly interview candidates who are referred members of the Whire network Make hiring decisions and then pay for successfully hired candidates For more information on Whire visit whire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpaca Cup</title>
      <link>https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/alpaca-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ziggy6792.github.io/projects/alpaca-cup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Alpaca Cup is an event management application for hosting and scoring competitions. The app has already been used in wakeboarding and wakeskating competitions all over the world, and we hope to branch out in other extreme sports in the future (such as skateboarding).
Alpaca Cup serves 2 main purposes;
Sharing event information (who is in each round, when rounds start, who progress to the next round) Sharing results for each round in realtime (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
